{ "cards": [
    {
        "front": "intrinsic content size",
        "back": "Every view has one in the vertical and horizontal direction"
    },
    {
        "front": "If you do not specify constraints on a view that explicitly determine the width or height. ",
        "back": "The view will derive its width or height from it intrinsic content size"
    },
    {
        "front": "Implicit constraints are derived from a views.",
        "back": "content hugging priorities and content compression resistance priorities."
    },
    {
        "front": "4 content priorities are.",
        "back": "horizontal content hugging priority, vertical content hugging priority, horizontal content compression resistance priority, vertical content compression resistance priority"
    },
    {
        "front": "Content hugging and compression priorities can range in value from:",
        "back": "0 to 1000"
    },
    {
        "front": "Content hugging priorities",
        "back": "how much a view resists getting bigger that is intrinsic content size"
    },
    {
        "front": "Content compression priorities",
        "back": "How much a view resists getting smaller than its intrinsic content size"
    },
    {
        "front": "A content hugging priority of 1000 means",
        "back": "View cannot get bigger that is intrinsic content size on that dimension(vertical or horizontal)."
    },
    {
        "front": "A content compression priority of 1000 means",
        "back": "View cannot get smaller that is intrinsic content size on that dimension."
    },
    {
        "front": "Ambiguous layout occurs when between 2 views.",
        "back": "If the priority is the same."
    },
    {
        "front": "Content priorities can be accessed in the applicable views",
        "back": "Size inspector."
    }
]
}
